本字幕由NEW字幕组译制
仅供英语交流学习使用  严禁用于商业途径
NEW字幕组招新群：720899169
快来加入我们  欢乐做剧
翻译: 柴  沈格子  ringo  爱抠脚的猪  杀手佩  平果猫  没戴眼镜听不清  江湖  木落  西比鹅
时间轴: 空集  超能力是吃  Katerina  没戴眼镜听不清
校对: Katerina  耳屎可以吃
总监: 耳屎可以吃
在互联网发展早期
In the early days of the Internet,
你是没法在线观看电影
you couldn't stream movies
或订泰餐送到家门口的
or summon Thai food to your doorstep.
但...  要是你对即将开课的物理讲座的
But... if you were interested in text-based news
相关文本新闻感兴趣的话
about upcoming physics lectures,
生活在那个时代简直棒极了
it was a great time to be alive.
我的天
Holy moly.
爸爸
Dad.
Dad!
-我在洗澡  -紧急情况
- I'm in the shower! - It's an emergency.
好吧  进来
Fine! Come in.
爸爸
Dad?
我以为你急着上厕所
I thought you had to use the bathroom.
这才早上7点23
It's 7:23 in the morning?
要是你不看时间表  那我打印的意义何在呢
Why do I print out schedules if you're not going to read them?
直接说你想干嘛
Tell me what you want.
下周末我们要干嘛
What are we doing next weekend?
-这听起来并不像紧急情况  -就是
- This ain't sounding like an emergency. - It is.
史蒂芬·霍金要开讲座
Stephen Hawking is giving a lecture,
我一定要去
and I really need to go.
能等我洗完澡再说吗
Can we talk about this when I'm out of the shower?
洗快点
Pick up the pace.
那份你不看的时间表写了
According to the schedule that you don't read,
还有六分钟就该我洗了
I'm due in there in six minutes.
*要说强壮我第一*
*Nobody else is stronger than I am*
*昨天移山无人敌*
*Yesterday I moved a mountain*
*你的英雄就是我*
*I bet I could be your hero*
*小小身躯大智慧*
*I am a mighty little man*
《小谢尔顿》
第三季  第十六集
所以能去吗
So can we go?
不知道
I don't know.
去洗澡啊
Go take a shower.
我还有2分15秒
I still have two minutes and 15 seconds.
先把这事儿解决了
Let's nail this down.
讲座在哪儿开
Where's the lecture?
要是在达拉斯  那去不了
And if the answer's Dallas, we're not going.
-好消息  不是达拉斯  -那在哪儿
- Good news, it's not Dallas. - Where?
加州  帕萨迪纳市
Pasadena, California.
加州
California?
那比达拉斯还远得很啊
That's a lot further than Dallas.
直线距离为1983千米
1,232 miles further as the crow flies.
看来你的地理很不错啊
But kudos to you for being up on your geography.
我们不可能去加州的
There's no way we're going to California.
要是史蒂芬·霍金坐轮椅都能去
If Stephen Hawking can make it there in a wheelchair,
我相信我们也可以的
I'm sure we can manage.
谢尔顿  机票很贵的
Sheldon, airplane tickets are expensive.
酒店也很贵  我们没钱
Hotels are expensive. We can't afford it.
可是他身体很虚弱
But his health is fragile.
这可能是我见到他本人的唯一机会了
This might be my only chance to ever see him in person.
我很抱歉  伙计
I'm sorry, buddy.
我很想继续谈
I would like to discuss this further,
但我只剩...
but I only have...
22秒就得洗澡了  解纽扣还要花时间
22 seconds to be in the shower, and buttons slow me down.
这就是我们输球的那一刻
This is the moment we lost that game.
一次失利不意味着我们要就此放弃
But one bad play doesn't mean you give up.
明明有充足的时间扭转局势
We had plenty of time to turn it around,
你们却直接放弃了比赛
but y'all decided it was over.
我不想再看到你们这样
I don't want to ever see that happen again.
下一次  即使觉得赢不了
Next time something seems out of your reach,
不准放弃
you do not quit.
给我更努力
You just dig deeper.
是不是说  只要我找到买得起的机票
Does that mean if I find an affordable flight to California,
就能去加州了
we can go?
麦德福旅行社
你好  有什么我能帮你的吗
Hi. Can I help you?
我想给我和我爸  找飞加州
I'm trying to find the cheapest flight to California
最便宜的航班
for me and my father.
好啊  请坐吧
Okay. Well, have a seat.
看来你是要去迪士尼啊
You lookin' to go to Disneyland?
我唯一想乘坐的过山车
The only ride I'm interested in is the intellectual roller
是史蒂芬·霍金驰骋的思维
coaster of Stephen Hawking's mind.
请问那在什么地方呢
And where is that located?
史蒂芬·霍金的脑袋里
Well... Stephen Hawking's head.
远在帕萨迪纳的加州理工学院
But that will be at Caltech in Pasadena.
明白了
Got it.
那你想在哪一天飞呢
And, uh, when were you looking to fly?
下个周末
Next weekend.
那没几天了啊
Oh, wow, that's pretty soon.
临时买机票会很贵哦
Traveling last-minute can be pricey.
有打折活动吗
Are there any discounts available?
有什么飞行常客项目的会员吗
Are you a member of any frequent-flier programs?
没有  从没坐过飞机
No. I've never flown before.
要节省机票钱可以
Well, ways to keep the cost down are:
在工作日飞  多次中转  或者...
flying on weekdays, multiple layovers, or...
或许对你不适用  不过...
This probably doesn't apply, but...
如果家庭中有人亡故
Airlines offer special fares
航空公司会提供特价机票
if there's been a death in the family.
有意思  可以借用下电话吗
Interesting. May I use your phone?
喂
Hello?
还有别的办法吗
What else you got?
喂
Hello?
再见
See ya.
-你要去哪儿  -和加娜出去玩
- Where you going? - Out with Jana.
你最近老跟她在一起啊
You've been spending a lot of time with her lately.
她是你女朋友吗
Is she your girlfriend?
爸  能让她别八卦吗
Dad, can you make her stop?
可以但不会  再说  我没那本事
Yeah, I could but I won't. Also, I can't.
我只是想了解你的近况
I just want to know what's going on in your life.
要是这姑娘是你心上人的话
And if this girl is someone special to you,
妈妈得知道呀
then she's special to me.
拜托
Come on.
玛丽  别问了
Mary, enough.
干嘛  我想知道嘛
What? I want to know.
拜拜
Bye.
说一句  爸不操心你
If it helps, I don't care.
嗯  谢啦
It does. Thank you.
他为什么啥也不想告诉我
Why doesn't he tell me anything?
你青春期的时候  会跟你爸妈说这些吗
When you were a teenager, did you tell your parents stuff?
不会
Well, no.
那你凭啥指望他会
Then why do you expect him to?
因为我是一个又酷又有趣的妈妈
'Cause I'm a cool, fun mom.
爸  好消息  去加州的飞机票
Dad, good news. Airline tickets to California
比你想象中的便宜多了
are more affordable than you think.
谢尔顿  我们不去
Sheldon, we're not going.
怎么了
What's all this about?
斯蒂芬·霍金要在加州理工开讲座
Stephen Hawking is giving a lecture at Caltech.
要是我们周三出发  而且能接受在博伊西
If we leave on Wednesday and are willing to make four layovers,
丹佛  阿尔伯克基  法戈转机的话
in Boise, Denver, Albuquerque and Fargo,
我们每人只要花95块钱
we can get there for only $95 each.
我还得工作  周三不可能陪你去
I have a job... I can't just leave in the middle of the week.
那妈妈呢
W-Well, then what about Mom?
抱歉  谢利  我们没办法去
Sorry, Shelly, we're not in a position to do this.
可斯蒂芬·霍金是我的偶像
But Stephen Hawking's my hero.
这就相当于你有机会见到耶稣  或是
Imagine if you got a chance to see Jesus or...
爸能见到发明啤酒的人一样
Dad got to meet the man who invented beer.
看样子有人遇到难题[内裤打结]了啊
Someone's Underoos are in a knot.
我的内裤穿着挺舒服的  谢谢关心
My Underoos are fitting just fine, thank you.
那你怎么看起来坐立不安的
Then why is there a stick up your butt?
别再问我屁股的问题了
Stop making inquiries about my bottom.
我喜欢
But I enjoy it.
爸妈不同意带我去加州
Mom and Dad won't take me to California
听斯蒂芬·霍金的讲座
to see Stephen Hawking.
-你居然觉得他们会带你去加州  -是啊
- You thought they would take you to California? - Yes.
我要买这本书他们都不肯
They wouldn't even buy me this book at the book fair.
害得我只能去图书馆借
I had to get it at the library.
这书上还粘着鼻屎
There's a booger on one of the pages.
这次不去  我可能再也没机会见到他本人了
Well, I may never get another chance to see him in person.
忍着  大家一直都依你
Suck it up. You always get everything you want.
瞎说
That's not true.
你有电脑
You got a computer.
-我在看鼻屎书  -行吧
- I'm reading a booger book. - Fine.
那要怎么"忍气吞声"呢
How do you recommend I "Suck it up"?
不知道  不如意的时候就
I don't know, when you don't get your way,
闭嘴  接着过
shut up and move on.
-你就这么干的  -对
- Is that what you do? - Yeah.
知道你为什么没电脑了吧
And that's why you don't have a computer.
乔吉是我儿子  我有权知道
Georgie is my son... I have the right to know
他和谁在一块儿
who he's spending time with.
你说加娜
You talking about Jana?
你也认识她
You know her?
严格来说并不认识
Well, I don't really know her.
我在戴尔店里
I've seen them hanging out together
看到过他们几次
at Dale's store a couple of times.
挺可爱的
She's cute.
很好  知道的比还我多
Great. So you know even more than I do.
这不正常吗
Always have.
我没觉得我过线了啊  我就想
I don't feel I'm being out of line wanting to...
知道这姑娘几岁了
know how old this girl is
去哪个教堂  姓什么
or what church she goes to or her last name.
姓欧文斯
Owens.
干嘛  这不告诉你了吗
What? Now you know.
难以置信
Unbelievable!
拜托
Oh, geez,
你担心谢尔顿不正常
you worry about Sheldon not being normal,
现在又担心乔吉太正常
now you're worried about Georgie being normal...
我怎么养出你这个二愣子
How did I raise such a turd?
我才不是  那啥
I am not...that word.
如果你都说不出那啥
If you can't say the word,
你估计就是那啥了
you might be the word.
接下来的几天
Over the next few days,
我尝试了我姐的建议
I tried to take my sister's advice
"忍气吞声"
and "Suck it up."
但怎么可能
But how could I,
所有一切都让我联想到史蒂芬·霍金
when everything reminded me of Stephen Hawking?
x-u-é  学
L-e-a-r-n.
正确  现在拼
That is correct. Now spell...
天哪
Oh, dear!
这其实是女士洗发水
It's actually a shampoo for ladies,
但我的秀发天生适用
but my hair just responds to it.
你周五晚上有空吗
So, what are you doing Friday night?
有空
No plans.
我爸妈正好不在家
My parents are gonna be out of town.
真的吗
Really?
想过来吗
Wanna come over?
你家人不在的话  我爸妈不会允许的
My parents won't let me if your folks ain't there.
好吧
Okay.
但我可以不告诉他们
Uh, but I guess I don't have to tell 'em.
行
Cool.
好  下课
Okay, that's it.
什么都没法帮我摆脱郁闷
Nothing was able to shake me from my doldrums,
连斯特奇斯博士炫酷的新毛绒背心也不行
not even Dr. Sturgis's jaunty new sweater-vest.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
嗯
Yes?
看你心不在焉啊
You seem distracted.
我真的很想去加州理工  看史蒂芬·霍金的讲座
I really wanted to see Stephen Hawking speak at Caltech,
但我爸妈没钱去
but my parents can't afford the trip.
太可惜了
That's too bad.
霍金博士的讲座特别精彩
Dr. H puts on a heck of a show.
我想是的
I believe it.
知道我这毛绒背心两面穿的
Would it make you feel better to know
会不会让你开心一点
this vest is reversible?
一点点吧  谢谢
A little. Thanks.
等等
Wait.
我也许能帮你去
I may be able to help you with Hawking.
真的吗
Really?
充满惊喜的可不止我这毛绒背心哦
This vest is not the only thing that's full of surprises.
你要去哪儿
Where ya goin'?
出去
Out.
去哪
Out where?
加娜家
Jana's.
她父母在家吗
Her parents gonna be there?
-是的  -好
- Yep. - Okay.
我打电话确认一下
Let me just call and make sure.
欧文斯
Owens.
那是她的姓吧  欧文斯
That's her last name, right? Owens?
你怎么这么奇怪
Why are you being so weird?
我没有很奇怪啊  你奇怪吗
I'm not being weird. Are you?
-我不啊  -很好
- No. - Good.
没人奇怪
No one's being weird.
别打
Don't call 'em.
为什么
Why not?
你怎么就不相信我呢
Why can't you just trust me?
因为我知道你在撒谎
Because I know that you're lying.
啥  我没有
What? No, I'm not.
我听到你跟加娜通的电话了
I heard you on the phone with Jana.
你监视我
You spied on me?
我不是有意的  但我很庆幸我听到了
I didn't mean to, but I'm glad that I did,
因为你当着我的面撒谎了
because you just lied to my face.
你哪儿也别想去
You are not going anywhere.
倒是拦我啊
Try and stop me.
你走出那扇门一步我就叫你爸来
You walk out that door, and your father gets involved.
我受不了了
I don't need this.
见鬼
Dang.
爸
Dad.
-你错过了一场好戏  -发生了什么
- You missed everything. - What happened?
乔吉要去跟加娜独处  对妈妈撒了谎
Georgie lied to Mom to be alone at Jana's house,
妈知道他撒谎了  因为她偷听了他俩通话
but Mom knew 'cause she listened in on his phone call.
天啊
Oh, boy.
现在乔吉被禁足了  大家都很不爽
Now he's grounded and everyone's mad.
我例外  我非常开心
Not me. I'm super happy.
行吧  拜拜
Well... bye.
爸  学校出钱让我们去加州
Dad, the university offered to pay for us to go to California!
他们还给我们订了酒店
They're even putting us up in a hotel.
真的吗
You're kidding.
我们要去加州了
We're going to California?
不  就我和爸爸去
No, just me and Dad.
真公平呢
That's fair.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
有时候讽刺的话会很明显
Sometimes sarcasm was laid on so thick
就连我都感觉得到
even I could detect it.
谢谢
Thanks!
但这一次我没感觉到
This was not one of those times.
好吧  不  这很说得通
I see. Well, no, that makes sense.
好的  约翰  谢谢
Okay, John, thanks.
再见
Bye.
谢尔顿是对的
Sheldon was right.
他们会支付旅程的所有开销
They're offerin' to pay for the whole trip.
为什么
Why?
斯特奇斯跟他上司谈了
Sturgis talked to his boss, and
他们真的很想招谢尔顿进学校
they really want to keep Sheldon goin' to school there.
我应该可以带他去
I guess I could take him.
为什么是你带他  他先问的我
Why you? He asked me first.
我现在很生乔吉的气
I'm mad at Georgie right now.
我们最好保持点距离
It'd be good for us to have some space.
所以  你和乔吉吵架
So, you pick a fight with Georgie,
就不让我去加州
and I don't get to go to California?
行吧  你去
Fine, you can go.
多谢
Thank you.
换个时区安排谢尔顿的如厕时间表
Have fun managing Sheldon's bathroom schedule
一定会很有趣
in different time zones.
我来给我们家要远行的大宝贝们拍个合影
Let me get a picture of my boys before their big trip.
做好记录是明智之举
It's smart to document this.
等你下次再见到我  我就是跟
Next time you see me, I'll have been in the presence
斯蒂芬·霍金见过面的人了
of Stephen Hawking.
笑一笑
Smile.
我觉得应该严肃一点
I'd prefer to look serious.
这照片可能有一天会印在课本上
This may appear in a textbook someday.
说"斯蒂芬·霍金"
Say, "Stephen Hawking."
-斯蒂芬·霍金  -斯蒂芬·霍金
- Stephen Hawking. - Stephen Hawking.
讨厌啦  你害我笑了
Aw, you made me smile.
洗手吃饭了
Wash up for dinner.
我不吃
I ain't eatin'.
那你也不能看电视了
Well, you're not watchin' TV.
不让我出门  现在连电视也不让我看了
I can't leave the house, and now I can't watch TV.
没错  因为你在关禁闭
Yeah, it's called being grounded.
真等不及要搬出去了
I can't wait to move out.
你说啥
What was that?!
下次我在电话上说
Next time, I'll say it on the phone,
你就能听清了
so you can hear me.
再这么皱眉头就要长皱纹了啊
You keep frownin' like that, you're gonna get wrinkles
跟你姥姥我似的
like your meemaw.
你挺美的啊
You look great.
我知道  我就是想听你说出来
I know, I just wanted to hear you say it.
你想什么呢
What's on your mind?
谢尔顿总是想要什么就有什么
Sheldon always gets everything he wants.
应该是吧
I guess he does.
是不太公平哈
That's not fair, huh?
可不是嘛
No!
不过话说回来  他只是
On the other hand, he's just
去听个科学讲座
going to some science lecture.
我知道  但是他就能坐飞机去加州
I know, but he gets to go on a plane to California.
坐飞机也没那么好
Planes aren't all that great.
飞机上都不让抽个烟
You can't even smoke on 'em anymore.
我跟你说啊
I tell you what,
你今天训练结束以后
after practice today,
咱们俩去找点乐子
you and me will do somethin' fun.
我能抽烟吗
Can I have my first cigarette?
不行
No!
那我能打耳洞吗
Can I get my ears pierced?
你妈妈不会喜欢的
Your mom won't like that.
所以  没准可以哦
So, maybe.
好嘞  34排AB座  咱们到了
All right, 34A and B... This is us.
你想靠过道还是靠窗
All right, you want the aisle or the window?
哪个是分配给我的
Which one is assigned to me?
都行  你随便选一个坐
It doesn't matter, just pick one.
如果靠窗坐  我就能看到起飞和降落
Well, if I sit by the window, I can watch the takeoff and landing,
如果靠过道坐
but if I sit on the aisle,
我就离厕所近一点
I'm closer to the bathroom.
又来了
Here we go.
如果靠窗的话  我上厕所的时候
Although if I'm by the window, you'll have
你就得起身让我出去
to get up when I use the bathroom.
反过来  你上厕所的时候
But if I'm not, I'll have
我就得站起来
to get up when you use the bathroom.
就随便选一个吧
Just pick one.
太难选了
It's a tricky decision.
我的膀胱比你的小...
My bladder's smaller than yours...
有什么问题吗
Everything okay here?
马上就好  来
About to be. Here!
靠过道坐
Aisle it is!
我们好了
We're good.
好的
Oh, okay.
能帮我一下吗
You want to help me with this?
不能
No.
是你对我撒谎了
You're the one who lied to me.
我不打算再跟你讲话  所以不会再对你撒谎了
Well, I'm done talkin' to you, so it'll never happen again.
怎么了
What?
我知道你不想跟我讲话  没关系
I know you don't want to talk, and that's fine.
你听我说就行了
You can just listen.
就算你做出正确的决定  生活就已经够难的了
Life is hard enough if you make good decisions,
但如果你做出错误的决定  生活只会难上加难
but if you make bad ones, it gets even harder.
我跟加娜根本就不会发生什么
Nothin' was gonna happen with Jana.
-乔治  -别说了
- Georgie... - No!
你总是把我往最坏的方面设想
You always assume the worst with me.
很抱歉你以前是个好孩子  而我就是个烂摊子
I'm sorry you were a perfect kid and I'm just a screwup.
你不是个烂摊子
You are not a screwup.
我也不是个好孩子
And I was not a perfect kid.
那你做过什么  某天早上做礼拜的时候睡着了
Oh, what'd you do, sleep through church one mornin'?
那我告诉你
For your information...
我曾逃过课
I used to skip class...
就为了
so that I could
去我男朋友的卡车里喝酒
drink beer in my boyfriend's truck.
老爸那时还有辆卡车
Dad had a truck back then?
说的不是你爸
Not talkin' about your dad.
我还...
I also...
偷开过你外婆的车
stole your meemaw's car
结果撞到沟里去了
and crashed it into a ditch.
是吗
Really?
和那个不是老爸的男朋友一起吗
With that boyfriend who wasn't Dad?
-这不是重点  -如果重点是
- Missin' the point! - If the point is
你做过错的决定  但现在还好好的
you made some bad decisions and turned out fine,
那干嘛对我这么严格
then why you being so hard on me?
因为有些决定你逃不开
Because some decisions you cannot walk away from
并且会影响你的余生
and they will affect the rest of your life.
如果你是在担心加娜怀孕的话
If you're talkin' about Jana getting pregnant,
不会的
she ain't gonna.
我当年也是这么想的  结果下一秒
That is what I thought, and the next thing I know,
我就站在礼堂里成为新娘了
I'm at the courthouse gettin' married.
你是奉子成婚的
You got married because you were pregnant?
是的
Yes.
所以我就是个错误
So, I was a mistake?
不不不
No! No!
你是上帝的恩赐
You are a blessin'.
我的错在于向我父母撒谎
The mistake was lyin' to my parents,
然后去你爸家过夜
so that I could spend the night at your dad's house.
接下来  就是龙舌兰的错了
And, you know, tequila.
女士们先生们  我是本次航班的机长
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your captain speaking.
我们即将出发前往洛杉矶
We're expecting a smooth flight to Los Angeles.
起飞前  请集中注意力
Before we take off, please direct your attention
听乘务员讲解
to the flight attendants as they review
几点重点安全事项
some important safety procedures.
"安全事项"  天啊
"Safety procedures"? Oh, baby.
请花几秒钟找到
Take a minute to locate
离你最近的出口
the exit closest to you.
最近的出口可能就在你后面
The nearest exit could be behind you.
如客舱突然遭到释压
Should the cabin experience sudden pressure loss,
氧气面罩会自动从座椅上方脱落
oxygen masks will drop down from above your seat...
客舱内怎么会释压呢
Why would the cabin lose pressure?
-不会的  -请将氧气面罩像这样罩在口鼻处
- It won't. - Place the mask over your mouth and nose,
拉动绳子将其系紧
like this, pull the strap to tighten it.
如果您携带儿童
If you are traveling with children,
请确保自己先佩戴好面罩
make sure that your own mask is on first
再去帮您的孩子戴好
before helping your child...
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this at all.
只是打个预防针
It's just a precaution.
其实  安全得很
You know... perfectly safe.
在极少数情况下  会需要水上降落和人员撤离
In the unlikely event of a water landing and evacuation...
水上降落  水上降落  水上降落
Water landing, water landing, water landing...
我做不到
I can't do this.
继续讲  我们马上回来
Keep going, we'll be right back.
先生
Sir?!
-谢尔顿  出来  -不要
- Sheldon, come out of there! - No!
至少开开门
At least open the door.
告诉他们我要下飞机
Tell them I need to get off.
先生
Sir?
你们俩都得回到座位上
You both need to return to your seats.
稍等
Just one second.
先生  先生
Sir. Sir...
如果你想见到斯蒂芬·霍金
If you want to see Stephen Hawking,
我们就要马上坐好
we have to sit down right now.
-太危险了  我做不到  -有点害怕没事的
- It's too dangerous. I can't! - It's okay to be scared.
-先生  -这就是你应该勇敢面对的时刻
- Sir? - Th-That's when you got to dig deep and be brave.
你说呢
So, what do you say?
不行  我现在害怕极了
No, I'm your terrified little boy!
好吧
Okay.
先生  拜托  他们要叫警卫了
Sir, please, they're gonna call security!
再等一下
Just one more second.
斯波克先生[《星际迷航》角色]
Mr. Spock!
他整天坐着宇宙飞船飞来飞去
He flies around all the time in that spaceship.
他不害怕  对吗
He's not afraid, is he?
我不是斯波克先生
I'm not Mr. Spock.
我知道  但我见过你假扮成他
No, but-but I've seen you pretend to be him.
你现在能试试吗
Could you do that right now?
你当斯波克  我当柯克[《星际迷航》角色]
You be Spock, I'll be Kirk.
试试吧
Maybe.
好的  斯波克先生
Okay, Mr. Spock.
首先你要回到座位上
Your first order is to return to your seat.
是  柯克船长
Aye, Captain.
空乘人员  准备起飞
Flight attendants, prepare for takeoff.
没事吧  斯波克先生
You okay, Mr. Spock?
尽我所能  长官
Doing my best, sir.
船长和斯波克不牵手的
The captain and Mr. Spock don't hold hands.
不好意思
Sorry.
好吧  就牵这一次
Okay, maybe just this once.
加利福尼亚理工学院
我觉得我们在加州的事上被骗了
I think we've been lied to about California.
校园里没有一个人被晒黑了
No one on this campus is tan at all.
是啊  一点都不黑
No, they are not.
想想这些桌子前
Imagine all the stimulating conversations
讨论多振奋人心
that must go on at these tables.
我赌也是
I bet.
我能想象有一天我也会来到这儿
I can see myself going here one day.
我想你能很好地适应的
I think you'd fit right in.